Olawale Sheriffdeen Olatunde Personal Summary:

With my years of experience as a business student and having done my level 5 in business and 80 credits toward a business administration degree, my skills revolve around organizational management, leadership, strategic and tactical planning.

Fb.com/dsheriffola

Personal Information

DOB: 11 August 1992

Gender: Male

ID Number: 67666753568

Cellphone: 08101653746

Address: Alhaja Olatunde's house, 2nd Avians, New garage Ibadan.

sheriffempire@gmail.com; olatundemaxy@gmail.com

Languages: English, Pidgin English and Yoruba

Educational Qualifications

Diploma: Cabin Crew Executive 2019

PAR-AVION INSTITUTE OF AVIATION &MANAGEMENT SCIENCES, NIGERIA

Higher Certificate in Business Administration 2014

TSIBA EDUCATION

Modules passed include:

- Business communication
- Business Numeracy
- Economics
- IT (Computer Literacy)
- Financial Management
- Leadership and Self- development
- Business Management

High School Certificate

2007

Merit comprehensive high school.

Ibadan, Oyo State.

Additional Courses and Training

•	EducoAfrica- Personal Development and Leadership	2013
•	Gender Reconciliation International	2013
•	Zeta web training Institute- Call Center	2013
•	Pulse Training -Fire Fighting and Prevention	2012
•	Windows Application	

Work Experience

2008

Natashan. 29 Wresch road, Observatory, Cape Town

Position: Advertising Consultant June 2017- December 2017.

Job Description:

In- House presentation of the Health product; Aqua Ozone Elite

FISH ON THE ROCKS, Hout Bay, Cape Town

February 2016-February 2018

Position: Waiter

YMCA Athlone, Cape Town

Project Manager Intern

January-February 2014

Duties included:

- Event Planning
- Research and Analysis
- E-mailing and data capture

SCARABEO 7 Oil Rig Project-

Position: Fire Man

March 2014- October 2014

Duties included:

- Eradication of fire hazards on board.
- Safety in the vessel
- Team work
- Fire prevention.

Shiata Guest House, Agbowo, Ibadan, Oyo State.

Position: Hotelier

December 2010 - January 2011

Duties include:

- Customer services
- Bedding, bathrooms and cleaning

Varsity Clubs and Societies

- Peer Educator at TSIBA Education
- Debate Society
- Students Assisting Homeless Children (SACH)

Personal Skills

- Organizational management
- Project management -Tactical and Execution Stages
- Interpersonal relations
- Counseling
- Coaching and Life skills catalyst
- Strategic planning
- Keyboard skills

- Communication skills
- Computer Skills
- Research and Internet
- Team Player

Relevant Experiences:

- Globacom Nigeria TV Commercial- Lead role
- Nigeria Idol TV Commercial- Lead Extra
- Etisalat TV Commercial- Extra

Hobbies

Outdoor

Hiking

Speaking

References

Sonja Hagins

Head of Support

TSiBA Education

Mutual, Pinelands.

+27832706521

Mrs. Najmuneesa Broderick.

CEO,

Fish on the rocks,

Hout bay.

+27834418282

Ms. Waseela

General Manager,

Natashan, Observatory, Cape Town.

+27843279050.

Mr. Ryan Benjamin Project Manager YMCA, Athlone, Cape Town +27715701653.